ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: ACTWU Begins Organizing at Four Other JPS Plants, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. May 26, 1978
  - Item 4: ACTWU Withdraws Charges in Laurens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. May 23, 1978
  - Item 5: Anderson Man Joins Fabrics Firm, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Appeal Court Upholds Ruling, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Daily Herald. September 7, 1978
  - Item 7: Boycott J. P. Stevens Textile Products, 1976; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Daily Cardinal November 11, 1976
  - Item 8: Coming Attractions, 1984, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: County Jobs Decline: S.C. Lost Most Textile Employees, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Anderson Independent. February 28, 1978
  - Item 10: Court Makes a Mockery of J. P. Stevens' Rights, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Shelby Daily Star. February 23, 1978
  - Item 11: Hill Joins West Point-Pepperell, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: J. P. Stevens Agrees To Treat All Employes Fairly, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: J. P. Stevens and Co., 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Greenville News. March 9, 1978
  - Item 14: J. P. Stevens Co., Blacks and Unions, 1976; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Baltimore Afro- American. December 11, 1976
  - Item 15: J. P. Stevens Draws More Fire, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Greenville News and Piedmont. March 18, 1978
  - Item 16: J. P. Stevens Switching From Hosiery, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Hickory Daily Record. March 7, 1978
  - Item 17: JPS Say Presbyterians Against Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. May 31, 1978
  - Item 18: Labor Pains: Now, The Senate's Got 'Em, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Layoffs Alleged At Starr Mills, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Legislators Seek To Aid Brown Lung Victims, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Anderson Independent. March 9, 1978
  - Item 21: Lung Group Assails Delay, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. May 25, 1978
  - Item 22: Meeting In Greenville: Stevens Benefits, Union Campaign Draw Criticism, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Anderson Independent. March 8, 1978
  - Item 23: Methodists of Area Clarify Boycott Position, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Daily Herald.
  - Item 24: Names In The News, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The News and Observer. May 31, 1978
  - Item 25: Needle Trades Show Scheduled, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: New Inroads, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Victor Riesel.
  - Item 27: New NLRB Charge Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    St. Louis Labor Tribune. December 23, 1976
  - Item 28: New Rule Due in '77 On Cotton Dust, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Daily News Record. August 16, 1977
  - Item 29: Pay Case Settled, But Wiretap Charges Linger, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Macon Telegraph. September 8, 1978
  - Item 30: Pro-Union J. P. Stevens Worker Reinstated, 1976; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 31: Reactionaires Attempt Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Knoxville Journal. January 17, 1977
  - Item 32: Rehire Workers, Stevens Ordered, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Greensboro Daily News. May 16, 1978
  - Item 33: Report of Anti-Union (SPFFF) Meeting, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    March 19, 1978.
  - Item 34: Stevens Agrees to Checkoff, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 35: Stevens Brings Meeting South, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Albany Herald. March 7, 1978
  - Item 36: Stevens Faces New Pressure, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 37: Stevens Fighting Back Publicly, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Charlotte Observer. April 2, 1978
  - Item 38: Stevens Headquarters is Sought, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Greenville News. March 16, 1978
  - Item 39: Stevens Hikes Employes' Pay, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The News and Observer. June 1, 1978
  - Item 40: Stevens Increases Union Talks, Official Says, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 41: Stevens Is An Embarrassment, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Hickory Daily Record.
  - Item 42: Stevens Rejects Union Resolutions, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Albany Herald. March 8, 1978
  - Item 43: Stevens Stockholders To Hold Meeting In South, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Atlanta Journal and Constitution. March 5, 1978
  - Item 44: Stevens Would Find Welcome In Greenville, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 45: Stevens, NLRB Reach Accord, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Greenville News. September 14, 1978
  - Item 46: Stevens, Union Rest Before Next Round, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The News and Observer. May 28, 1978
  - Item 47: Textile Division Names Officers, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 48: Textile Group Says Keep Import Levies, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 49: Textile Union Wants 15% Wage Hike, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Charlotte Observer. May 23, 1978
  - Item 50: The Bottom Line: J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 51: The Right To Organize, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    St. Louis Labor Tribune. August 30, 1979
  - Item 52: Thinking of Signing a Union Card? Read This!, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Passed out at Stuart, VA
  - Item 53: Union Engages Two Clergymen, Nun In Campaign Against J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Religious News Service. August 3, 1978
  - Item 54: Union Objects To Report, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 55: Union Pushing Stevens Hearing, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 56: Union Strategist: He Tilts With Stevens, In Boardrooms, and Wins, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 57: Union Will Add Organizers In Drive at J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Winston-Salem Journal and Sentinel. March 30, 1978
  - Item 58: What Is The Real J. P. Stevens Issue, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 9)
    The Charlotte Observer. March 28, 1978